What you see on the bottom of the screen
is the updated version of the heart rate
monitor, or
heart rate variability
and heart rate,
and it's got it tuned to be sort of
smoother as opposed to
more jittery. It's
just gonna be running throughout.
My heart rate starting, or my heart rate
variability is starting at
51 tonight or something like that.
I'm not sure what it shows right now, I
can't quite see it, but I'll work on that next,
and
we'll see what it does.
Last night,
my heart rate variability improved a bit.
I don't remember what the numbers were, but
it
doesn't really matter.
I've got
it logged.
And again, the whole purpose of this is
I discovered accidentally that the thing
I'm about to do
seems to be really good.
It sort of seems to give you mental boost,
cardio boost,
helps me with sleep, et cetera.
And it's a very simple activity.
And let's go ahead and get started. So